ILR School Dean's Annual Reports /3088
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
ILR School Dean's Annual Reports
1945-1985
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Ives, Irving M.
Emerson, Lynn A.
Neufeld, Maurice F.
Shank, Donald J.
Risley, Robert F.
McConnell, John W.
Moore, David G.
McKersie, Robert B.
Doherty, Robert
/3088
3 cubic feet
3 linear ft.
Records (documents).
ILR Dean's annual reports to the University President, for the first 40 years of the school.
3082384
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
M. Clark, January 25, 2016
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, September 20, 2016
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Irving, Ives, M.; Emerson, Lynn A.; Neufeld, Maurice F.; Shank, Donald J.; Catherwood, M. P. (Martin Paul), 1904-1978; Risley, Robert F. (Robert Francis), 1922-; McConnell, John W.; Moore, David G.; McKersie, Robert B.; Doherty, Robert; New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations; New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations. Dean's Office
3082384
- Dean's Report to the President - 1945-46, 1945-1946 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Dean's Report to the President - 1946-47, 1946-1947 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Dean's Report to the President - 1947-48, 1947-1948 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Dean's Report to the President - 1948-49, 1948-1949 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Dean's Report to the President - 1949-50, 1949-1950 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Dean's Report to the President - 1951-52, 1951-1952 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Dean's Report to the President - 1950-51, 1950-1951 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Dean's Report to the President - 1952-53, 1952-1953 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Dean's Report to the President - 1953-54, 1953-1954 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Dean's Report to the President - 1954-55, 1954-1955 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Dean's Report to the President - 1955-1956 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Dean's Report to the President - 1956-57, 1956-1957 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Dean's Report to the President - 1957-58, 1957-1958 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Dean's Report to the President - 1958-59, 1958-1959 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Dean's Report to the President - 1959-60, 1959-1960 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Dean's Report to the President - 1960-61, 1960-1961 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Dean's Report to the President - 1961-62, 1961-1962 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Dean's Report to the President - 1962-63, 1962-1963 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Dean's Report to the President - 1963-64, 1963-1964 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Dean's Report to the President - 1964-65, 1964-1965 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Dean's Report to the President - 1965-66, 1965-1966 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Dean's Report to the President - 1965-66 (1 of 2), 1965-1966 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Dean's Report to the President - 1965-66 (2 of 2), 1965-1966 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Dean's Report to the President - 1966-67, 1966-1967 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Dean's Report to the President - 1967-68, 1967-1968 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Dean's Report to the President - 1967-68 (bound edition), 1967-1968 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Dean's Report to the President - 1968-69, 1968-1969 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Dean's Report to the President - 1969-70, 1969-1970 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Dean's Report to the President - 1970-71, 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Dean's Report to the President - 1971-72, 1971-1972 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Dean's Report to the President - 1972-73, 1972-1973 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Dean's Report to the President - 1973-74 (1 of 2), 1973-1974 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Dean's Report to the President - 1973-74 (2 of 2), 1973-1974 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Dean's Report to the President - 1973-74 (1 of 2), 1973-1974 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Dean's Report to the President - 1973-74 (2 of 2), 1973-1974 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Dean's Report to the President - 1974-175, 1974-1975 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Dean's Report to the President - 1975-76, 1975-1976 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Dean's Report to the President - 1976-77, 1976-1977 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Dean's Report to the President - 1977-78, 1977-1978 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Dean's Report to the President - 1978-79, 1978-1979 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Dean's Report to the President - 1978-79, 1978-1979 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Dean's Report to the President - 1979-1980 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Dean's Report to the President - 1979-1980 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Dean's Report to the President - 1980-1981 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Dean's Report to the President - 1980-1981 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Dean's Report to the President - 1981-1982 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Dean's Report to the President - 1984-1985 (Box 3, Folder 9)